You bastard
你这个混蛋
Hey, baby ,when you get home?
嘿   宝贝你什么时候回来的
I thought you wouldn't be out of cleaners until Friday,
我以为你周五才会出去洗东西
Yeah, I bet you did think that ,you cheating jerk
是吧   我猜你也是这样想的   你这个花心的混蛋
It's not what you think
这不是你想的那样
What is it then?
那是哪样
I just got lonely
我只是寂寞了
Certainly true
这绝对是真的
What is she talking about, Lebron? Tell me what?
她在说些什么你能解释一下吗
I don't know what she is talking about?
我不知道她在说些什么
Girl, he was just using you,
妹子   他只是在利用你
you are just a side chick,
你只是可有可无的
why do you think he only mess with you during the season,
你知道为什么她只给你发短信而不愿意和你说话吗
he is with me when it really matters
而这才是真正重要的事
Baby Don't listen to her, please
宝贝   不要听她说   求你
Baby, turn off the light, I am sleepy,
宝贝   把电话关掉吧   我好困
Oh, hell, no
哦   老天   不要
All I did for you, I gain all these weight to cover up your headline,
我一直站在你这边   我用尽全力帮你解释头条,
We even took our talents to South-Beach together, how   could you, Lebron? How could you?
你怎么可以这样 你怎么可以
Sorry, baby,don't cry.
对不起   宝贝   不要哭
This is just a one time,
这只是一次
two time, three time, four time, five time,
两次   三次   四次   五次
six time,seven time thing, why you got a trip?
六次   七次的事情   不要想的太严重了